Blanchard, Duncan; Papers ua902.065
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1900-2003; 3; 7.8 cubic ft.
  - Resch, Francois, 1977; 1979-1987 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Resch, Francois, 1988-1991; 1944; 1998; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Ricci, John, 1992; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Rick, Ted, 1959; 1962; 1967-1968; 1970-1971 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Rick, Ted, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Rogers, R.R., 1982 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Rolland, Ernest, 1954; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Root-Bernstein, Robert, 1996-1997 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Rooth, Charles, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Rossing, Thomas, 1973-1974; 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Ruknke, Lothar, 1962; 1967; 1975 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Ryan, Bob, 1969-1970; 1976; 1991; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - S-, 1949; 1951-1955; 1959; 1961-1962; 1964 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - S-, 1966-1968; 1971-1989; 1991; 1995; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Salkever, Louis, 1971; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Salomons, Wim, 1982; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Sandt,Donald, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Saunders, Peter, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Schaefer, Vincent J., 1949-1951; 1953-1957; 1959-1961; 1963-1970 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Schaefer, Vincent J., 1971-1975; 1977; 1980-1981; 1983; 1985-1987 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Schaefer, Vincent J., 1989; 1992-2000; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Schaefer, Vincent J. - Hawaiian Islands Research, 1963-1964 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Schechter, Robert, 1998-1999; 2001; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Schnell, Russ, 1973-1975; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Serpolay, Roger, 1968-1970; 1972; 1988-1989 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Severynse, Gerry, 1965 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Show, Glenn, 1993; 1998 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Shaval, Hillel, 1978; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Sieburth, John, 1963-1964; 1976-1978; 1982-1983 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Skop, Richard, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Smagerinsky, Joseph, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Smith-Johanssen, Robert, 1965; 1997; 1999 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Spencer, A.T., 1966; 1968-1972; 1974; 1979; 1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Spencer, A.T., Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Spengler, John, 1964; 1967 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Spengler, John, 1972; 1974; 1989; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Spiel, Donald, 1991-1993; 1995-1997 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Squires, Patrick, 1954-1955; 1957; 1974 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Stommel, Hank, 1982; 1984 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Stowt, Glenn, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Stow, C.D., 1979; 1984; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Strahler, Arthur, 1974 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Summerhayes, Roger, 1996-2003 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Sutcliff, W.H., 1965-1966; 1972-1975; 1977-1978; Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Syzdek, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971; 1974-1981 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Syzdek, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986; 1989-1991; 1993; 1995-1998; 2000 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Syzdek, Larry [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 71)
  - T-, 1954-1955; 1965-1966; 1968-1969; 1973; 1975 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 72)
  - T-, 1978; 1980-1982; 1984-1986; 1997; 2000 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - T-, Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Takahashi, T., 1976-1977; 1984 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Geoffrey, 1962; 1967; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Taylor, John J., 1971-1973; 1980; 1984; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Ronald C., 1964; 1974; 1979-1983; 1994 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Thompson, Gertrude, 1980-1984; 1986; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Thorpe, S.A., 1982-1984; 1987-1989 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Toba, Yoshiak, 1960; 1963; 1965-1969; 1971-1972; 1978 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Toba, Yoshiak, 1980; 1982-1984; 1990-1991 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Toland, Ray, 1976; 1978; 1984; 1998 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Trefethan, Lloyd, 1976-1977; 1983-1985; 1987-1992; 1995-1996; 2001 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Twitchell, Paul, 1971-1972; 1975-1976; 1980 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - U-, 1972; 1982; 1984; 1987 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - V-, 1953; 1963; 1973-1976; 1990-1992; 1994 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, 1950-1959; 1962-1963; 1965-1969; 1973; 1976-1977 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, 1980-1981; 1983-1990; 1992-1999; 1789/2003 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - W-, 1953-1955; 1957; 1960; 1963-1978 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - W-, 1980-1989; 1991; 1994; 1999; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Weber, Martin E, 1979-1984; 1988; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Wegner, Peter, 1974-1975; 1978-1979 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Wickman, Helmut, 1953; 1958; 1971; 1978-1979 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Wickman, Helmut, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Weisel, Cliff, 1981-1992 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Went, Frits W., 1960; 1964-1965 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - William, Jack, 1996-1997 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Wise, George, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1953; 1956-1957; 1959-1961; 1963; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1964-1968; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1967-1969 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1972-1976 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1977-1978 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1980-1982 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1983-1985 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1986-1988 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1989-1992 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Woodcock, Al, 1993-2002 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Woodcock, Al [Letters from family, friends, and colleagues], 1983-1984; Undated (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Woolf, David, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Wu, Jin, 1979; 1982; 1985; 1988-1990; 1992 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Wu, Jin, 1995; Undated (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - X, Y, Z, 1965; 1968; 1971-1972; 1974-1975; 1981-1987 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
- Subject Files, 1926-2003; 4; 3.8 cubic ft.
  Series 4 documents Dr. Blanchards professional activities from his time at the University of New York at Albany. While materials from the Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute are also included, they make up a smaller part of the series. The focus of the materials is on grant applications, meetings and Conferences, and classes Dr. Blanchard taught.
  The materials included in the series are photographs, negatives, correspondence, postcards, invitations, event programs, pamphlets, brochures, newspaper and magazine clippings, journal articles, notes (handwritten and typed), drafts, figures, class outlines, grant applications and proposals, proposal evaluations, memos, grant outlines, grant account abstracts, and reports.
  Folder names reflect Dr. Blanchards own naming system but arrangement has been changed to allow for easier use.
  - The Behavior of Waterdrops at Terminal Velocity in Air (1950), 1926; 1947; 1949-1951 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - The Behavior of Waterdrops at Terminal Velocity in Air (1950), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Class Outlines, 1968; 1970-1975; 1977-1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Cloud Seeding, 1982-1984; 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Grants, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Grants- Electrical Charges and Bacterial Concentrations- 1st Year, 1980-1982; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Grants- Film Drops and the Marine Sea Salt- 1st Year, 1981-1984; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Grants- Film Drops and the Marine Sea Salt- 2nd Year, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Grants- NSF Grant: Account No.020-706-A(February 1976-July 1978, 1976-1979; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Grants- NSF Grant: No.320-0852A(March 1978- August 1980), 1977-1980; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Grants- NSF Mechanism for Water-to-Air(August 1970 to February 1976), 1970-1976; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Grants- NSF Support(1958-1968) at Woods Hole, 1958-1959; 1961-1968 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Grants- NSF Support(1958-1968) at Woods Hole, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Grants NSF: The Water-to-Air Transfer and Iodine(May 1970), 1970-1972 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Grants- Production and Size, Distribued of Film and Jet Drops, 1988; 1789/2003 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Grants- Relative Importance of Jet Film Drops, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Grants- Second Year of res. F 320 1076A, 1981-1984; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Grants- Size Distribution and Mode of Formation- 1st Year, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Grants- Size Distribution and Mode of Formation- 2nd Year, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Humar, 1947; 1957; 1960-1961; 1963; 1965 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Humar, 1969; 1971-1983; 1988-1989; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Lecture Notes, 1948; 1968; 1971-1973; 1975-1976; 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Lecture Notes, 1983-1984; 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Meetings and Conferences, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Meetings and Correspondence- 0-Gravity(Huntsville) (Skeet Vaughn, 1972-1973), 1972-1974; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AAAS Elec. Nom. Comm. (1980-1984) [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Meetings and Conferences- ACS Meeting (September 1979), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Adirondack Confrence on Electrostatics (1968), 1957; 1968-1969; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Aerobiology Meeting (April 4-6, 1979, Minneapolis), 1978-1979; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Aerosols: N.Y. Academy of Science (January 1979), 1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AGU-AMS Meeting (21-25 April 1969), 1968-1969; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AGU Fall Meeting (December 1975), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Air- Sea Interaction Panel (1964-1965), 1963-1965; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Meetings and Conferences- American Physics Society Meetings(St. Lawrence University, 23-24 September 1983), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Meetings and Conferences- American Society Microbiology Ann. Meeting (7-12 March 1982), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AMS Air-Sea Interaction Comm. (1972-1974), 1972-1975 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AMS Air-Sea Meeting (1-3 December 1971, Ft.Lauderdale), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AMS Cloud Physics Panel (1973), 1973-1974; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Meetings and Conferences- AMS Ocean-Atmos. Conf. (1 Feburary 1980, LA, Cal.), 1979; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Meetings and Conferences- APS Meeting (Feburary 1976), 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Meetings and Conferences- ASRC Art Museum Project (October-November 1993), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Atmos.-Elec. Meetings (Mountreux, Switz., 6-10 May 1963), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Bentley Talk at Stowe, Vermot (8 Feburary 1987), 1986-1987; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Bentley Talk, Trinity College (1991), 1990-1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Bentley Tape for Albany Institute (1983), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Book Reviews at the Schenectady Public Library, 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Meetings and Conferences- China Trip (1990-1991), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Cloud Physics Confrence Woods Hole (September 1955), 1955-1956; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Cloud Physics Meeting (Japan 1965), 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Colloid and Surface Chemistry Meeting (Chicago, 27-31 August 1973), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Comm. Of "Producing Scholars" (1975), Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Committee on Industrial Linkages (SUNYA, 1981), 1981-1983; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Comm. To Review the Dean (1978) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Condensation Nuclei Confrence (France, May 1963), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Condensation Nucleus Conferences (6th International at Albany and Pa., 1966), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Confrence on Marine Meteor. (Virginia Beach, 7-10 September 1966), 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Council on Reasearch (SUNYA, 1976-1977), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Meetings and Conferences- The Cyclic Exchange Between Sea-Salt and Organic Material (AGU-AMS Symptoms, April 1981, 1961; 1976; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Ecology Award Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Environmental Factors Influencing the Performance of Naval Weapon Systems (1959), 1962; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Estuarine Res. Fed MTG. (New Orleans, October 1987), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Ethics Committee (1989), 1981; 1983; 1985-1986; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Evaluation of the ONR Applied Research Program (14 April 1988), 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Four Lectures to Advanced Course in Phys. Ocean. And Marine Meteor. (August 1963--VO HDI) [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Gordon Confrence (8-12 August 1983), 1980; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Gordon Research Confrence (11-15 August 1980), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Int. Comm. On Atmos. Electricity (1967), 1967-1968; 1971; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Int. Conf. Cloud Physics (Toronto, 26-30 August 1968), 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Interpoll III (27-31 October 1980, Miami), 1980-1981; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Interpoll IV (19-23 May 1981, Tallinn, USSR), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Meetings and Conferences- IUGG Grenoble (August- September 1975), 1974-1975; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Junge's 65th Birthday Symposium (July 1976), 1976-1977; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Lecture Given at "Course for Industry" (1-5 December 1958), 1958-1960 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Lycoming College (October 1977), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Maritime Met. Workshop (8-9 September 1977), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Meetings and Conferences- National Research Council Res. Assoc. Program Eval. (23-24 February 1989), 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Meetings and Conferences- NATO Adu. Study Inst. (Air-Sea Interaction, 1982), 1981-1982; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Meetings and Conferences- NCAR Meeting at O'Hare Airport on Hawaii Cloud Physics Work, 1963 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Ocean Dumping (EPA-NAS, 1974), 1974-1976; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Ocean Sciences Meting (AGU, ASLO- New Orleans, 13-17 January 1986), 1985; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Meetings and Conferences - ONR Air-Sae Workshop (23 April 1986), 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Meetings and Conferences- ONR Workshop on Bubbly Media (Rosslyn, Va.)23-25 May 1983, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Meetings and Conferences- ONR Workshop on the Chemistry and Biology of the Sea Surface Interface (Sanibel Island Florida), 1989 October 23-25 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Paper for NAS (25 April 1964), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Paul Lemon Award Committee [RESTRICED], 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Phlips Lectures (November 1973), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Project Themis (1967-1973), 1966; 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Rutgers Talk (11 April 1984), 1983-1984 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Meetings and Conferences -Sea-to-Air Chemistry (Ft. Lauderdale, 31 January- 3 February 1972), 1971; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Sea- Air Chemistry Meeting (France, October 1973), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Search Committee for ASRC Director (1974), 1974-1975; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Search Committee for U.P for Res. And Grad Studies (1978) [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980; 1789/2003 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Searex Review (1 May 1979), 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Meetings and Conferences- S.C. Acad. Sci. (March 1976) (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Second International Symposium, Microbial Ecology (1980), 1979-1980; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Seminar at University of Delaware at Lewes (12 April 1989), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Symposium, Aerobiology (Ottawa, 7-9 June 1989) (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Symposium at University of Conn. (6-7 Oct 1988) (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Symposium at University of Montreal (1-3 June 1988), 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Talk at Meeting of Mass. Assoc. of Sci. Supervisors (7-8 May 1987), 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Task Force on Grad. Students (SUNYA,1976), 1976-1977 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Third Gordon Res. Conference (10-14 August 1987), 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Meetings and Conferences- University of Delaware Visit (August 1991), 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Visiting Scientist Programs (1966 anad 1969), 1966-1971; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Weather Modification Assn. (Albany, 1-4 October 1980), 1949; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Whitecap Workshop (Galway, Ireland, 4-7 September 1983), 1982-1983; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Woods Holes Cloud Physics Conference (June 1959), Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Workshop Correspondence, 1974; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Workshop on the Sea Surface Microlayer (Washington, D.C., 18-19 December 1985), 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Meetings and Conferences- Yellowstone Expedition (1963), 1962-1964; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Monsanto, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - National Youth Science Foundation, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Project Cirrus, 1947-1950; 1952-1953; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Project Cirrus, 1991; 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Project Cirrus- "The Electrical Charging of Surfaces Produced by the Impact of High Velocity Soild Particles", 1945 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Project Cirrus- First and Fourth Quarterly Progress Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Project Cirrus- Meteorological Research, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Project Cirrus- Occasional Reports Numbers 1-4, 1948 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Project Cirrus- Occasional Reports Numbers 7 and 10, 1948 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Project Cirrus- Occasional Reports Numbers 15-17, 1949 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Project Cirrus- Occasional Reports Numbers 23-30, 1950-1951 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Project Cirrus- A Preliminary Report on Flight 45 of Project Cirrus Concerned with the Seeding of Cummulus Clouds in New Mexico, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Project Cirrus- Widespread Control of Weather by Silver Iodide Seeding, 1955 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Retirement (1989), Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Script For AMS/ESI Film, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Script For AMS/ESI Film, 1965-1967; 1969; 1974-1975; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)